<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zvezda on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</title>
    <link>//models.bulimov.me/tags/zvezda/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Zvezda on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;small&gt;  &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Creative Commons License&#34; style=&#34;border-width:0&#34; src=&#34;//i.creativecommons.org/l/by-sa/4.0/80x15.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Content licensed under a &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License&lt;/a&gt;, except where indicated otherwise.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//models.bulimov.me/tags/zvezda/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[WIP] Varyag, 1/350, Zvezda</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/zvezda-varyag/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/zvezda-varyag/</guid>
      <description>Protected Cruiser Varyag Built in USA in 1899 for the Imperial Russian Navy, Varyag became very famous in Russia after the Battle of Chemulpo Bay. In that battle, she got trapped in the bay and tried to break out by fighting against Japanese squadron. Sadly she scored no hits on the enemy, lost 31 men dead and 191 injured, returned back to the bay and got scuttled.
The Russian government took the opportunity to turn this very unsuccessful battle into a publicity stunt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medieval Lifeboat, 1/72, Zvezda</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/zvezda-medieval-lifeboat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/zvezda-medieval-lifeboat/</guid>
      <description>Boat It&amp;rsquo;s essentially the same boat type as the one I&amp;rsquo;ve built from wood, and in same scale. This made it particularly fun to build as I was able to directly compare both builds.
Model quality It&amp;rsquo;s very good, the wooden texture is beautifully executed, and the were no flash at all. My only tiny complaint is about seam lines, but as there were so few details it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sovremenny (Современный) Russian Destroyer, 1/700, Zvezda</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/zvezda-sovremenny/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/zvezda-sovremenny/</guid>
      <description>Neat modern kit by Zvezda. The model is tiny, details are crisp, and build is straightforward bar the challenge of working with such small parts. I&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed building it a lot, much more than I expected - normally I don&amp;rsquo;t do anything modern.
Russian Destroyer &amp;ldquo;Sovremenny&amp;rdquo; (Современный). Commissioned in 1980, this ship was the first destroyer built by USSR in 20 years. This fact is reflected in ships name - &amp;lsquo;Sovremenny&amp;rsquo; means &amp;lsquo;modern&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;contemporary&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HMS Hood, 1/720, Italery/Zvezda</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/zvezda-hood/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/zvezda-hood/</guid>
      <description>Italery kit from 1978, which explains strange 1/720 scale.
I&amp;rsquo;ve got Zvezda version just because it was a present. Interesting fact - Zvezda is not allowed to sell this kit outside of ex-USSR because it&amp;rsquo;s just cheaper in it&amp;rsquo;s version.
The Mighty HMS Hood Built in 1918, the only ship in her class, this battlecruiser remained the largest and most powerful warship for 20 years. She tragically sank during the Battle of the Denmark Strait with the loss of all but 3 of her crew of 1418 men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I-4, 1/72, Zvezda</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/zvezda-i-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/zvezda-i-4/</guid>
      <description>This model attracted me because of it&amp;rsquo;s subject. This Tupolev I-4 plane is little known even amongst ex-USSR modellers despite being first Soviet all-metal fighter. And it&amp;rsquo;s a sesquiplane, which is also interesting to me.
Model quality If you think that nothing surprising here, because it&amp;rsquo;s old Zvezda, here comes the surprise - it&amp;rsquo;s actually not. It&amp;rsquo;s Zvezda making Encore Models kit from ninetieth. So the quality is even a bit worse then I expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BA-10 (БА-10), 1/35, Zvezda</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/zvezda-ba-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/zvezda-ba-10/</guid>
      <description>My first completed model after a 6 year hiatus.
Started to build it in 2009, it was the first model I&amp;rsquo;ve used airbrush on. Tried salt chipping on it (with totally inappropriate base color). Then I simply didn&amp;rsquo;t have time or space for model making, and only after moving to Dublin in 2016 I finally got back to this wonderful hobby.
So just to get my grip on it back, I&amp;rsquo;ve finished this one.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
