<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2022 on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</title>
    <link>//models.bulimov.me/tags/2022/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2022 on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;small&gt;  &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Creative Commons License&#34; style=&#34;border-width:0&#34; src=&#34;//i.creativecommons.org/l/by-sa/4.0/80x15.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Content licensed under a &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License&lt;/a&gt;, except where indicated otherwise.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//models.bulimov.me/tags/2022/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HMS Terror, 1/75, OcCre</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/occre-terror/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/occre-terror/</guid>
      <description>Once I built up some confidence with wooden kits, especially after St. Gabriel I felt confident enough to start the &amp;lsquo;proper&amp;rsquo; wooden ship. Like you know, one which you have to plank manually and scratch-build most of the stuff. As you probably know, picking the right subject you are really interested in is the key to success. Especially when built is expected to take many months. After careful considerations and reading Model Ship World a lot, I picked this kit from OcCre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2022 Year in Review</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/2022-year-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/2022-year-in-review/</guid>
      <description>I like the ‘year in review’ format I tried for the first time last year, so here we go again.&#xA;No point in sugarcoating it - 2022 was a terrible, terrible year, with horrible war starting in Europe. Of course this affected all parts of my life, including hobbies, as I was too depressed and anxious to bring myself back to it.&#xA;Eventually I managed (or rather forced myself) to do at least some modelling, if anything because it calms me and improves my mental health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FT-17, 1/35, Meng</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/meng-ft17/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/meng-ft17/</guid>
      <description>Legendary Renault FT-17, most influential and revolutionary tank design in history. It&amp;rsquo;s so tiny by modern standards that 1/35 model feels like 1/48. That&amp;rsquo;s why it&amp;rsquo;s even more interesting and challenging to build it with full interior.&#xA;Model quality It&amp;rsquo;s just perfect, even compared to modern Airfix kits. No flash, very dense and hard plastic allowing amazing level of details, and very detailed build manual. It&amp;rsquo;s the best plastic kit I&amp;rsquo;ve ever built.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Varyag, 1/350, Zvezda</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/zvezda-varyag/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/zvezda-varyag/</guid>
      <description>Protected Cruiser Varyag Built in USA in 1899 for the Imperial Russian Navy, Varyag became very famous in Russia after the Battle of Chemulpo Bay. In that battle, she got trapped in the bay and tried to break out by fighting against Japanese squadron. Sadly she scored no hits on the enemy, lost 31 men dead and 191 injured, returned back to the bay and got scuttled.&#xA;The Russian government took the opportunity to turn this very unsuccessful battle into a publicity stunt.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
