<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2024 on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</title>
    <link>//models.bulimov.me/tags/2024/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2024 on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;small&gt;  &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Creative Commons License&#34; style=&#34;border-width:0&#34; src=&#34;//i.creativecommons.org/l/by-sa/4.0/80x15.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Content licensed under a &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License&lt;/a&gt;, except where indicated otherwise.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//models.bulimov.me/tags/2024/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[WIP] HMS Alert, 1/48, Trident Models</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/trident-alert/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/trident-alert/</guid>
      <description>Since I started building wooden kits, I looked at the Plank-on-Frame models with great awe. Exposing the internal structure of the ship with all the beautiful complexity is extremely appealing to me as an engineer.&#xA;This year my wife convinced me to take the plunge and try to build one myself.&#xA;After building 10+ wooden models I felt confident enough to attempt building some small and well-made POF kit.&#xA;Seeing a group build for this model on Ships of Scale forums, along with the positive reviews and acceptable price (around 600EUR after import taxes) helped me to make the decision in favour of this kit from the new Chinese manufacturer Trident Models.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>[WIP] HMS Flirt, 1/64, Vanguard Models</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/vanguard-flirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/vanguard-flirt/</guid>
      <description>This model attracted me because of graceful, beautiful lines, and my desire to try a recent model by famous Chris Watton. After all, I quite enjoyed his design in Lady Nelson, and the kits from Vanguard Models had glowing reviews on a Model Ship World forum.&#xA;HM Brig Sloop Flirt There is nothing remarkable about ship herself. She was built in 1782 and had a relatively uneventful career in the Navy.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
