<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ships on </title>
    <link>http://models.bulimov.ru/categories/ships/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ships on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://models.bulimov.ru/categories/ships/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[WIP] Cannon Yolle 1801, 1/72, Master Korabel, 2018</title>
      <link>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/mk-cannon-yolle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/mk-cannon-yolle/</guid>
      <description>My first ever wooden kit, yay! I was always intimidated by wooden ship kits, assuming huge amount of scratch-building and crafting. Also I knew from my childhood plastic kit experience that rigging is quite challenging on Tall Ships.
Luckily nowadays thanks to modern technologies like laser cutters and CAD software wooden kits are enhanced with pre-shaped laser cut hull planks and details.
Considering this I decided to give it a try and build something relatively simple, relatively cheap and without complex rigging.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sovremenny (Современный) Russian Destroyer, 1/700, Zvezda, 2018</title>
      <link>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-sovremenny/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-sovremenny/</guid>
      <description>Neat modern kit by Zvezda. The model is tiny, details are crisp, and build is straightforward bar the challenge of working with such small parts. I&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed building it a lot, much more than I expected - normally I don&amp;rsquo;t do anything modern.
Russian Destroyer &amp;ldquo;Sovremenny&amp;rdquo; (Современный). Commissioned in 1980, this ship was the first destroyer built by USSR in 20 years. This fact is reflected in ships&amp;rsquo;s name - &amp;lsquo;Sovremenny&amp;rsquo; means &amp;lsquo;modern&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;contemporary&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HMS Hood, 1/720, Italery/Zvezda, 2018</title>
      <link>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-hood/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-hood/</guid>
      <description>Italery kit from 1978, which explains strange 1&amp;frasl;720 scale.
I&amp;rsquo;ve got Zvezda version just because it was a present. Interesting fact - Zvezda is not allowed to sell this kit outside of ex-USSR because it&amp;rsquo;s just cheaper in it&amp;rsquo;s version.
The Mighty HMS Hood Built in 1918, the only ship in her class, this battlecruiser remained the largest and most powerful warship for 20 years. She tragically sank during the Battle of the Denmark Strait with the loss of all but 3 of her crew of 1418 men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harbour Tug boat &#39;Lucky XI&#39;, 1/108, Revell, 2016</title>
      <link>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/revell-harbour-tug/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/revell-harbour-tug/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I&amp;rsquo;ve been in San Francisco Maritime National Historical Park and seen Hercules tug there, I knew I want to build something like it.
Quick research on scalemates.com showed that only reasonable option I had was this ancient Revell kit from 1979, so I had no choice but to build it.
Model quality As you might expect from a kit designed in 1955, the quality is bad by modern standards.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>