<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ships on </title>
    <link>//models.bulimov.ru/categories/ships/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ships on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//models.bulimov.ru/categories/ships/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>SS Jeremiah O&#39;Brien Liberty Ship, 1/700, Trumpeter, 2019</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/trumpeter-liberty-ship/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/trumpeter-liberty-ship/</guid>
      <description>SS Jeremiah O&amp;rsquo;Brien SS Jeremiah O&amp;rsquo;Brien is one of the few surviving Liberty Ships - cargo ships massively built by US in WW2. Used everywhere - from arctic convoys to D-Day, those ships became a legend.
This particular ship is currently based in San Francisco where I had the pleasure to see and visit her. Obviously after the visit I decided to build the model of this remarkable ship. I decided to go with 1&amp;frasl;700 scale, mostly because I already had HMS Hood in ~1&amp;frasl;700, but now I see how choosing this scale was a huge mistake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[WIP] HMS Terror, 1/75, OcCre, 2020</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/occre-terror/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/occre-terror/</guid>
      <description>Once I built up some confidence with wooden kits, especially after St. Gabriel I felt confident enough to start the &amp;lsquo;proper&amp;rsquo; wooden ship. Like you know, one which you have to plank manually and scratch-build most of stuff. As you probably know, picking the right subject you are really interested in is the key to success. Especially when built is expected to take many months. After careful considerations and reading Model Ship World a lot, I picked this kit from OcCre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boat 1763, 1/72, Falkonet, 2019</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/falkonet-wooden-boat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/falkonet-wooden-boat/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t really help it - wooden models attract me more and more. This one is yet another tiny boat kit that I bought for like 10 Euros on my trip to Russia.
The manufacturer is Falkonet, apparently they focus on smaller stuff like boats and yachts, no tall ships in the catalog so far.
Wooden boat from year 1763 Some luxurious wooden boat from Catherine The Great era. Well, basically a typical 6-oar boat with ornaments on the side.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>St. Gabriel, 1/72, Master Korabel, 2019</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/mk-st-gabriel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/mk-st-gabriel/</guid>
      <description>For some reason wooden kits keep attracting me more and more. This one is the third I&amp;rsquo;m building, all from the same Russian company called Master Korabel (Мастер Корабел).
St. Gabriel deck-boat This was the main ship of the First Kamchatka Expedition lead by Danish explorer Vitus Bering for Russian Tsar Peter The Great in 1724-1730.
Model quality Just as with previous kits from this company I had no major issues with the model, wooden parts are awesome and very well engineered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medieval Lifeboat, 1/72, Zvezda, 2019</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-medieval-lifeboat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-medieval-lifeboat/</guid>
      <description>Boat It&amp;rsquo;s essentially the same boat type as the one I&amp;rsquo;ve built from wood, and in same scale. This made it particularly fun to build as I was able to directly compare both builds.
Model quality It&amp;rsquo;s very good, the wooden texture is beautifully executed, and the were no flash at all. My only tiny complaint is about seam lines, but as there were so few details it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>English Carronade, 1/17, Mantua, 2018</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/mantua-english-carronade/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/mantua-english-carronade/</guid>
      <description>After I visited famous HMS Victory in Portsmouth this summer, I wanted to build something related to her.
My experience with wooden kits tells me that building the full HMS Victory model is a very big project that I&amp;rsquo;m not ready for yet, not to mention the sheer size of it. So building this kit allowed me to scratch that HMS Victory itch without spending a year on it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launch, 1/72, Master Korabel, 2018</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/mk-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/mk-launch/</guid>
      <description>As I had great fun building my first wooden kit, on my next trip to Russia I bought a bunch of other kits from local manufacturers. This modern kit is again from Russian company called Master Korabel (Мастер Корабел), is fully laser-cut and costs less than 10 Euros.
Launch This is just a general purpose boat used on sail ships in 17th century. Nothing really special about it.
Model quality Just as with previous kit from this company I had no issues, fit was almost perfect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cannon Jolle 1801, 1/72, Master Korabel, 2018</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/mk-cannon-yolle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/mk-cannon-yolle/</guid>
      <description>My first ever wooden kit, yay! I was always intimidated by wooden ship kits, assuming huge amount of scratch-building and crafting. Also I knew from my childhood plastic kit experience that rigging is quite challenging on Tall Ships.
Luckily nowadays thanks to modern technologies like laser cutters and CAD software wooden kits are enhanced with pre-shaped laser cut hull planks and details.
Considering this I decided to give it a try and build something relatively simple, relatively cheap and without complex rigging.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sovremenny (Современный) Russian Destroyer, 1/700, Zvezda, 2018</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-sovremenny/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-sovremenny/</guid>
      <description>Neat modern kit by Zvezda. The model is tiny, details are crisp, and build is straightforward bar the challenge of working with such small parts. I&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed building it a lot, much more than I expected - normally I don&amp;rsquo;t do anything modern.
Russian Destroyer &amp;ldquo;Sovremenny&amp;rdquo; (Современный). Commissioned in 1980, this ship was the first destroyer built by USSR in 20 years. This fact is reflected in ships&amp;rsquo;s name - &amp;lsquo;Sovremenny&amp;rsquo; means &amp;lsquo;modern&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;contemporary&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HMS Hood, 1/720, Italery/Zvezda, 2018</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-hood/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-hood/</guid>
      <description>Italery kit from 1978, which explains strange 1&amp;frasl;720 scale.
I&amp;rsquo;ve got Zvezda version just because it was a present. Interesting fact - Zvezda is not allowed to sell this kit outside of ex-USSR because it&amp;rsquo;s just cheaper in it&amp;rsquo;s version.
The Mighty HMS Hood Built in 1918, the only ship in her class, this battlecruiser remained the largest and most powerful warship for 20 years. She tragically sank during the Battle of the Denmark Strait with the loss of all but 3 of her crew of 1418 men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harbour Tug boat &#39;Lucky XI&#39;, 1/108, Revell, 2016</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/revell-harbour-tug/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/revell-harbour-tug/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I&amp;rsquo;ve been in San Francisco Maritime National Historical Park and seen Hercules tug there, I knew I want to build something like it.
Quick research on scalemates.com showed that only reasonable option I had was this ancient Revell kit from 1979, so I had no choice but to build it.
Model quality As you might expect from a kit designed in 1955, the quality is bad by modern standards.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>