<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2020 on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</title>
    <link>//models.bulimov.me/tags/2020/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2020 on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;small&gt;  &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Creative Commons License&#34; style=&#34;border-width:0&#34; src=&#34;//i.creativecommons.org/l/by-sa/4.0/80x15.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Content licensed under a &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License&lt;/a&gt;, except where indicated otherwise.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//models.bulimov.me/tags/2020/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[WIP] HMS Terror, 1/75, OcCre</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/occre-terror/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/occre-terror/</guid>
      <description>Once I built up some confidence with wooden kits, especially after St. Gabriel I felt confident enough to start the &amp;lsquo;proper&amp;rsquo; wooden ship. Like you know, one which you have to plank manually and scratch-build most of the stuff. As you probably know, picking the right subject you are really interested in is the key to success. Especially when built is expected to take many months. After careful considerations and reading Model Ship World a lot, I picked this kit from OcCre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Providence Whaleboat, 1/25, Artesania Latina</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/al-whaleboat/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/al-whaleboat/</guid>
      <description>With this small and simple kit I wanted to get a break from rigging HMS Terror I&amp;rsquo;ve been building for over a year now.
Providence Whaleboat Typical whaleboat used for whaling during the 19th century in New England. Such boats were carried on board of whaling ships and used to hunt and harpoon whales.
While I definitely disapprove whaling as a practice, the whaleboat itself is quite a beautiful subject.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four-oared yawl of XIX century, 1/24, Falkonet</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/falkonet-yawl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/falkonet-yawl/</guid>
      <description>Another wooden model. The more I build them, the more I love doing it.
The manufacturer is a Russian company called Falkonet, they specialize in extremely detailed kits.
Four-oared yawl of XIX century Not much to say about the subject, it&amp;rsquo;s a fairly typical yawl from that age. The box says it&amp;rsquo;s based on real historical plans from 19th century, by English shipwright Benjamin Stuckey.
Model quality It&amp;rsquo;s absolutely excellent, level of details is insane and superior to what I&amp;rsquo;ve seen in other manufacturer&amp;rsquo;s kits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SS Jeremiah O&#39;Brien Liberty Ship, 1/700, Trumpeter</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/trumpeter-liberty-ship/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/trumpeter-liberty-ship/</guid>
      <description>SS Jeremiah O&amp;rsquo;Brien SS Jeremiah O&amp;rsquo;Brien is one of the few surviving Liberty Ships - cargo ships massively built by US in WW2. Used everywhere - from arctic convoys to D-Day, those ships became a legend.
This particular ship is currently based in San Francisco where I had the pleasure to see and visit her. Obviously after the visit I decided to build the model of this remarkable ship. I decided to go with 1/700 scale, mostly because I already had HMS Hood in ~1/700, but now I see how choosing this scale was a huge mistake.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
