<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>vehicles on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</title>
    <link>//models.bulimov.ru/categories/vehicles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in vehicles on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;small&gt;  &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Creative Commons License&#34; style=&#34;border-width:0&#34; src=&#34;//i.creativecommons.org/l/by-sa/4.0/80x15.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Content licensed under a &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License&lt;/a&gt;, except where indicated otherwise.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//models.bulimov.ru/categories/vehicles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[WIP] FT-17, 1/35, Meng, 2018</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/meng-ft17/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/meng-ft17/</guid>
      <description>Legendary Renault FT-17, most influential and revolutionary tank design in history. It&amp;rsquo;s so tiny by modern standards that 1/35 model feels like 1/48. That&amp;rsquo;s why it&amp;rsquo;s even more interesting and challenging to build it with full interior.
Model quality It&amp;rsquo;s just perfect, even compared to modern Airfix kits. No flash, very dense and hard plastic allowing amazing level of details, and very detailed build manual. So far it&amp;rsquo;s the best kit I&amp;rsquo;ve ever built.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DUKW, 1/35, Italery, 2019</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/italery-dukw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/italery-dukw/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I was a passenger on one of this things thanks to Viking Splash Tours, I wanted to build this model. It&amp;rsquo;s remarkable that truck/boat hybrid built 70 years ago is still able to move, and even sail.
As for the model, I&amp;rsquo;ve got Eduard PE kit for it, because I really enjoyed working with PE while building HMS Hood, and it adds so much to the look.
The Mighty DUKW This remarkable vehicle is a modification of CCKW truck, and DUKW comes from:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Albion 3-Point Refueller, 1/48, Airfix, 2018</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/airfix-albion-refueller/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/airfix-albion-refueller/</guid>
      <description>Very good modern kit from Battle of Britain: Ready For Battle set.
The Albion 3-Point Refueller Not much information available online about this machines. Refuellers like this were in use with the RAF during the Battle of Britain. Apparently having 3 fuel hoses cut down the refuelling time.
Model quality Almost no flash, great detailed instructions, excellent fit, good decals. Just perfect.
Build notes The build was straightforward, no fit issues at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bedford MWD, 1/48, Airfix, 2018</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/airfix-bedford-mwd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/airfix-bedford-mwd/</guid>
      <description>Nice little model from Battle of Britain: Ready For Battle set.
The whole kit is fantastic - it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;new tool&amp;rsquo;, so perfect quality and level of details. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to start with truck just to learn how to paint vehicles and try some new techniques. It&amp;rsquo;s the first model I&amp;rsquo;ve painted after I read awesome Adam&amp;rsquo;s Armour book by Adam Wilder, so I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to apply knowledge I&amp;rsquo;ve got from the book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BA-10 (БА-10), 1/35, Zvezda, 2016</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-ba-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-ba-10/</guid>
      <description>My first completed model after a 6 year hiatus.
Started to build it in 2009, it was the first model I&amp;rsquo;ve used airbrush on. Tried salt chipping on it (with totally inappropriate base color). Then I simply didn&amp;rsquo;t have time or space for model making, and only after moving to Dublin in 2016 I finally got back to this wonderful hobby.
So just to get my grip on it back, I&amp;rsquo;ve finished this one.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
