<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Master Korabel on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</title>
    <link>//models.bulimov.me/tags/master-korabel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Master Korabel on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;small&gt;  &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Creative Commons License&#34; style=&#34;border-width:0&#34; src=&#34;//i.creativecommons.org/l/by-sa/4.0/80x15.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Content licensed under a &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License&lt;/a&gt;, except where indicated otherwise.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//models.bulimov.me/tags/master-korabel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>St. Gabriel, 1/72, Master Korabel</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/mk-st-gabriel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/mk-st-gabriel/</guid>
      <description>For some reason wooden kits keep attracting me more and more. This one is the third I&amp;rsquo;m building, all from the same Russian company called Master Korabel (Мастер Корабел).
St Gabriel deck-boat This was the main ship of the First Kamchatka Expedition lead by Danish explorer Vitus Bering for Russian Tsar Peter The Great in 1724-1730.
Model quality Just as with previous kits from this company I had no major issues with the model, wooden parts are awesome and very well engineered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Launch, 1/72, Master Korabel</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/mk-launch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/mk-launch/</guid>
      <description>As I had great fun building my first wooden kit, on my next trip to Russia I bought a bunch of other kits from local manufacturers. This modern kit is again from Russian company called Master Korabel (Мастер Корабел), is fully laser-cut and costs less than 10 Euros.
Launch This is just a general purpose boat used on sail ships in 17th century. Nothing really special about it.
Model quality Just as with previous kit from this company I had no issues, fit was almost perfect.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cannon Jolle 1801, 1/72, Master Korabel</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/mk-cannon-yolle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/mk-cannon-yolle/</guid>
      <description>My first ever wooden kit, yay! I was always intimidated by wooden ship kits, assuming huge amount of scratch-building and crafting. Also I knew from my childhood plastic kit experience that rigging is quite challenging on Tall Ships.
Luckily nowadays thanks to modern technologies like laser cutters and CAD software wooden kits are enhanced with pre-shaped laser cut hull planks and details.
Considering this I decided to give it a try and build something relatively simple, relatively cheap and without complex rigging.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
