<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</title>
    <link>http://models.bulimov.ru/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;small&gt;  &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Creative Commons License&#34; style=&#34;border-width:0&#34; src=&#34;//i.creativecommons.org/l/by-sa/4.0/80x15.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
      Content licensed under a &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License&lt;/a&gt;, except where indicated otherwise.
        &lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 23:39:58 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://models.bulimov.ru/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[WIP] Sovremenny (Современный), 1/700, Zvezda, 2018</title>
      <link>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-sovremenny/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 23:39:58 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-sovremenny/</guid>
      <description>Neat modern kit by Zvezda. The model is tiny, details are crisp, and build is straightforward bar the challenge of working with such small parts. I&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed building it a lot, much more than I expected - normally I don&amp;rsquo;t do anything modern.
Russian Destroyer &amp;ldquo;Sovremenny&amp;rdquo; (Современный). Commissioned in 1980, this ship was the first destroyer built by USSR in 20 years. This fact is reflected in ships&amp;rsquo;s name - &amp;lsquo;Sovremenny&amp;rsquo; means &amp;lsquo;modern&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;contemporary&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[WIP] DUKW, 1/35, Italery, 2018</title>
      <link>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/italery-dukw/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 19:23:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/italery-dukw/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I was a passenger on one of this things thanks to Viking Splash Tours, I decided to build this model. It&amp;rsquo;s remarkable that truck/boat hybrid built 70 years ago is still able to move, and even sail.
As for the model, I&amp;rsquo;ve got Eduard PE kit for it, because I really enjoyed working with PE while building HMS Hood, and it adds so much to the look.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HMS Hood, 1/720, Italery/Zvezda, 2018</title>
      <link>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-hood/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-hood/</guid>
      <description>Italery kit from 1978, which explains strange 1&amp;frasl;720 scale.
I&amp;rsquo;ve got Zvezda version just because it was a present. Interesting fact - Zvezda is not allowed to sell this kit outside of ex-USSR because it&amp;rsquo;s just cheaper in it&amp;rsquo;s version.
The Mighty HMS Hood Built in 1918, the only ship in her class, this battlecruiser remained the largest and most powerful warship for 20 years. She tragically sank during the Battle of the Denmark Strait with the loss of all but 3 of her crew of 1418 men.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bedford MWD, 1/48, Airfix, 2018</title>
      <link>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/airfix-bedford-mwd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/airfix-bedford-mwd/</guid>
      <description>Nice little model from Battle of Britain: Ready For Battle set.
The whole kit is fantastic - it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;new tool&amp;rsquo;, so perfect quality and level of details. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to start with truck just to learn how to paint vehicles and try some new techniques. It&amp;rsquo;s the first model I&amp;rsquo;ve painted after I read awesome Adam&amp;rsquo;s Armour book by Adam Wilder, so I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to apply knowledge I&amp;rsquo;ve got from the book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harbour Tug boat &#39;Lucky XI&#39;, 1/108, Revell, 2016</title>
      <link>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/revell-harbour-tug/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/revell-harbour-tug/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I&amp;rsquo;ve been in San Francisco Maritime National Historical Park and seen Hercules tug there, I knew I want to build something like it.
Quick research on scalemates.com showed that only reasonable option I had was this ancient Revell kit from 1979, so I had no choice but to build it.
Model quality As you might expect from a kit designed in 1955, the quality is bad by modern standards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I-4, 1/72, Zvezda, 2017</title>
      <link>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-i-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-i-4/</guid>
      <description>This model attracted me because of it&amp;rsquo;s subject. This Tupolev I-4 plane is little known even amongst ex-USSR modellers despite being first Soviet all-metal fighter. And it&amp;rsquo;s a sesquiplane, which is also interesting to me.
Model quality If you think that nothing surprising here, because it&amp;rsquo;s old Zvezda, here comes the surprise - it&amp;rsquo;s actually not. It&amp;rsquo;s Zvezda making Encore Models kit from ninetieth. So the quality is even a bit worse then I expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Albatros W.4, 1/72, Roden, 2016</title>
      <link>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/roden-albatros-w4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/roden-albatros-w4/</guid>
      <description>Another blast from the past.
Bought this model in 2010, just because I wanted to build some WW1 biplane. So it waited 6 years for me do find time and space to build it. Lucky for me, I didn&amp;rsquo;t even start it in 2010 except for gluing two engine halves together, so it wasn&amp;rsquo;t ruined and I had no problems with old paint.
Model quality I&amp;rsquo;ve built it right after BA-10, and the quality difference was drastic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BA-10 (БА-10), 1/35, Zvezda, 2016</title>
      <link>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-ba-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-ba-10/</guid>
      <description>My first completed model after a 6 year hiatus.
Started to build it in 2009, it was the first model I&amp;rsquo;ve used airbrush on. Tried salt chipping on it (with totally inappropriate base color). Then I simply didn&amp;rsquo;t have time or space for model making, and only after moving to Dublin in 2016 I finally got back to this wonderful hobby.
So just to get my grip on it back, I&amp;rsquo;ve finished this one.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>