<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>airplanes on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</title>
    <link>//models.bulimov.ru/categories/airplanes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in airplanes on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;small&gt;  &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Creative Commons License&#34; style=&#34;border-width:0&#34; src=&#34;//i.creativecommons.org/l/by-sa/4.0/80x15.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Content licensed under a &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License&lt;/a&gt;, except where indicated otherwise.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//models.bulimov.ru/categories/airplanes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Royal Aircraft Factory BE2c, 1/72, Airfix, 2019</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/airfix-be2c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/airfix-be2c/</guid>
      <description>Royal Aircraft Factory BE2c3  The Royal Aircraft Factory B.E.2 was a British single-engine tractor two-seat biplane designed and developed at the Royal Aircraft Factory. Most production aircraft were constructed under contract by various private companies, both established aircraft manufacturers and firms that had not previously built aircraft. Around 3,500 were manufactured in all.
 from wikipedia.
I picked this model on my visit to Royal Air Force Museum London. The museum is absolutely awesome, and they even have BE2b aircraft on display.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I-4, 1/72, Zvezda, 2017</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-i-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/zvezda-i-4/</guid>
      <description>This model attracted me because of it&amp;rsquo;s subject. This Tupolev I-4 plane is little known even amongst ex-USSR modellers despite being first Soviet all-metal fighter. And it&amp;rsquo;s a sesquiplane, which is also interesting to me.
Model quality If you think that nothing surprising here, because it&amp;rsquo;s old Zvezda, here comes the surprise - it&amp;rsquo;s actually not. It&amp;rsquo;s Zvezda making Encore Models kit from ninetieth. So the quality is even a bit worse then I expected.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Albatros W.4, 1/72, Roden, 2016</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/roden-albatros-w4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/roden-albatros-w4/</guid>
      <description>Another blast from the past.
Bought this model in 2010, just because I wanted to build some WW1 biplane. So it waited 6 years for me do find time and space to build it. Lucky for me, I didn&amp;rsquo;t even start it in 2010 except for gluing two engine halves together, so it wasn&amp;rsquo;t ruined and I had no problems with old paint.
Model quality I&amp;rsquo;ve built it right after BA-10, and the quality difference was drastic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
