<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Falkonet on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</title>
    <link>//models.bulimov.me/tags/falkonet/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Falkonet on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;small&gt;  &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Creative Commons License&#34; style=&#34;border-width:0&#34; src=&#34;//i.creativecommons.org/l/by-sa/4.0/80x15.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Content licensed under a &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License&lt;/a&gt;, except where indicated otherwise.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="//models.bulimov.me/tags/falkonet/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Leudo, 1/48, Falkonet</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/falkonet-leudo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/falkonet-leudo/</guid>
      <description>Leudo Leudo is a type of cargo ship, used in Mediterranean Sea to carry various goods. Of course, most people familiar with the subject will think about the wine-carrying type of Leudo, and that&amp;rsquo;s exactly what this model depicts.
Model quality This is an upgraded Pear version of the kit, so the material quality is very good.
But I have few issues with the design of the kit. Unlike Falkonet&amp;rsquo;s Yawl which was superb, this kit feels over-engineered to the point where it detracts from builder&amp;rsquo;s experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Four-oared yawl of XIX century, 1/24, Falkonet</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/falkonet-yawl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/falkonet-yawl/</guid>
      <description>Another wooden model. The more I build them, the more I love doing it.
The manufacturer is a Russian company called Falkonet, they specialize in extremely detailed kits.
Four-oared yawl of XIX century Not much to say about the subject, it&amp;rsquo;s a fairly typical yawl from that age. The box says it&amp;rsquo;s based on real historical plans from 19th century, by English shipwright Benjamin Stuckey.
Model quality It&amp;rsquo;s absolutely excellent, level of details is insane and superior to what I&amp;rsquo;ve seen in other manufacturer&amp;rsquo;s kits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boat 1763, 1/72, Falkonet</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/falkonet-wooden-boat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/falkonet-wooden-boat/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t really help it - wooden models attract me more and more. This one is yet another tiny boat kit that I bought for like 10 Euros on my trip to Russia.
The manufacturer is Falkonet, apparently they focus on smaller stuff like boats and yachts, no tall ships in the catalog so far.
Wooden boat from year 1763 Some luxurious wooden boat from Catherine The Great era. Well, basically a typical 6-oar boat with ornaments on the side.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
