<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>1/48 on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</title>
    <link>//models.bulimov.me/tags/1/48/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 1/48 on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;small&gt;  &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Creative Commons License&#34; style=&#34;border-width:0&#34; src=&#34;//i.creativecommons.org/l/by-sa/4.0/80x15.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Content licensed under a &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License&lt;/a&gt;, except where indicated otherwise.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;</copyright><atom:link href="//models.bulimov.me/tags/1/48/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[WIP] HMS Alert, 1/48, Trident Models</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/trident-alert/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/trident-alert/</guid>
      <description>Since I started building wooden kits, I looked at the Plank-on-Frame models with great awe. Exposing the internal structure of the ship with all the beautiful complexity is extremely appealing to me as an engineer.
This year my wife convinced me to take the plunge and try to build one myself.
After building 10+ wooden models I felt confident enough to attempt building some small and well-made POF kit.
Seeing a group build for this model on Ships of Scale forums, along with the positive reviews and acceptable price (around 600EUR after import taxes) helped me to make the decision in favour of this kit from the new Chinese manufacturer Trident Models.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leudo, 1/48, Falkonet</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/falkonet-leudo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/falkonet-leudo/</guid>
      <description>Leudo Leudo is a type of cargo ship, used in Mediterranean Sea to carry various goods. Of course, most people familiar with the subject will think about the wine-carrying type of Leudo, and that&amp;rsquo;s exactly what this model depicts.
Model quality This is an upgraded Pear version of the kit, so the material quality is very good.
But I have few issues with the design of the kit. Unlike Falkonet&amp;rsquo;s Yawl which was superb, this kit feels over-engineered to the point where it detracts from builder&amp;rsquo;s experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Albion 3-Point Refueller, 1/48, Airfix</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/airfix-albion-refueller/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/airfix-albion-refueller/</guid>
      <description>Very good modern kit from Battle of Britain: Ready For Battle set.
The Albion 3-Point Refueller Not much information available online about this machines. Refuellers like this were in use with the RAF during the Battle of Britain. Apparently having 3 fuel hoses cut down the refuelling time.
Model quality Almost no flash, great detailed instructions, excellent fit, good decals. Just perfect.
Build notes The build was straightforward, no fit issues at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bedford MWD, 1/48, Airfix</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/airfix-bedford-mwd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/airfix-bedford-mwd/</guid>
      <description>Nice little model from Battle of Britain: Ready For Battle set.
The whole kit is fantastic - it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;rsquo;new tool&amp;rsquo;, so perfect quality and level of details. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to start with truck just to learn how to paint vehicles and try some new techniques. It&amp;rsquo;s the first model I&amp;rsquo;ve painted after I read awesome Adam&amp;rsquo;s Armour book by Adam Wilder, so I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to apply knowledge I&amp;rsquo;ve got from the book.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
