<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2019 on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</title>
    <link>//models.bulimov.me/tags/2019/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2019 on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;small&gt;  &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Creative Commons License&#34; style=&#34;border-width:0&#34; src=&#34;//i.creativecommons.org/l/by-sa/4.0/80x15.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Content licensed under a &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License&lt;/a&gt;, except where indicated otherwise.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//models.bulimov.me/tags/2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HMS Terror, 1/75, OcCre</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/occre-terror/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/occre-terror/</guid>
      <description>Once I built up some confidence with wooden kits, especially after St. Gabriel I felt confident enough to start the &amp;lsquo;proper&amp;rsquo; wooden ship. Like you know, one which you have to plank manually and scratch-build most of the stuff. As you probably know, picking the right subject you are really interested in is the key to success. Especially when built is expected to take many months. After careful considerations and reading Model Ship World a lot, I picked this kit from OcCre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Royal Aircraft Factory BE2c, 1/72, Airfix</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/airfix-be2c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/airfix-be2c/</guid>
      <description>Royal Aircraft Factory BE2c3 The Royal Aircraft Factory B.E.2 was a British single-engine tractor two-seat biplane designed and developed at the Royal Aircraft Factory. Most production aircraft were constructed under contract by various private companies, both established aircraft manufacturers and firms that had not previously built aircraft. Around 3,500 were manufactured in all.&#xA;from Wikipedia.&#xA;I picked this model on my visit to Royal Air Force Museum London. The museum is absolutely awesome, and they even have BE2b aircraft on display.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SS Jeremiah O&#39;Brien Liberty Ship, 1/700, Trumpeter</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/trumpeter-liberty-ship/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/trumpeter-liberty-ship/</guid>
      <description>SS Jeremiah O&amp;rsquo;Brien SS Jeremiah O&amp;rsquo;Brien is one of the few surviving Liberty Ships - cargo ships massively built by US in WW2. Used everywhere - from arctic convoys to D-Day, those ships became a legend.&#xA;This particular ship is currently based in San Francisco where I had the pleasure to see and visit her. Obviously after the visit I decided to build the model of this remarkable ship. I decided to go with 1/700 scale, mostly because I already had HMS Hood in ~1/700, but now I see how choosing this scale was a huge mistake.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boat 1763, 1/72, Falkonet</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/falkonet-wooden-boat/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/falkonet-wooden-boat/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t really help it - wooden models attract me more and more. This one is yet another tiny boat kit that I bought for like 10 Euros on my trip to Russia.&#xA;The manufacturer is Falkonet, apparently they focus on smaller stuff like boats and yachts, no tall ships in the catalog so far.&#xA;Wooden boat from year 1763 Some luxurious wooden boat from Catherine The Great era. Well, basically a typical 6-oar boat with ornaments on the side.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DUKW, 1/35, Italery</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/italery-dukw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/italery-dukw/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I was a passenger on one of this things thanks to Viking Splash Tours, I wanted to build this model. It&amp;rsquo;s remarkable that truck/boat hybrid built 70 years ago is still able to move, and even sail.&#xA;As for the model, I&amp;rsquo;ve got Eduard PE kit for it, because I really enjoyed working with PE while building HMS Hood, and it adds so much to the look.&#xA;The Mighty DUKW This remarkable vehicle is a modification of CCKW truck, and DUKW comes from:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>St. Gabriel, 1/72, Master Korabel</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/mk-st-gabriel/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/mk-st-gabriel/</guid>
      <description>For some reason wooden kits keep attracting me more and more. This one is the third I&amp;rsquo;m building, all from the same Russian company called Master Korabel (Мастер Корабел).&#xA;St Gabriel deck-boat This was the main ship of the First Kamchatka Expedition lead by Danish explorer Vitus Bering for Russian Tsar Peter The Great in 1724-1730.&#xA;Model quality Just as with previous kits from this company I had no major issues with the model, wooden parts are awesome and very well engineered.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Medieval Lifeboat, 1/72, Zvezda</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/zvezda-medieval-lifeboat/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/zvezda-medieval-lifeboat/</guid>
      <description>Boat It&amp;rsquo;s essentially the same boat type as the one I&amp;rsquo;ve built from wood, and in same scale. This made it particularly fun to build as I was able to directly compare both builds.&#xA;Model quality It&amp;rsquo;s very good, the wooden texture is beautifully executed, and the were no flash at all. My only tiny complaint is about seam lines, but as there were so few details it wasn&amp;rsquo;t a problem.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
