<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Airfix on </title>
    <link>//models.bulimov.ru/tags/airfix/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Airfix on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="//models.bulimov.ru/tags/airfix/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Royal Aircraft Factory BE2c, 1/72, Airfix, 2019</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/airfix-be2c/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/airfix-be2c/</guid>
      <description>Royal Aircraft Factory BE2c3  The Royal Aircraft Factory B.E.2 was a British single-engine tractor two-seat biplane designed and developed at the Royal Aircraft Factory. Most production aircraft were constructed under contract by various private companies, both established aircraft manufacturers and firms that had not previously built aircraft. Around 3,500 were manufactured in all.
 from wikipedia.
I picked this model on my visit to Royal Air Force Museum London.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Albion 3-Point Refueller, 1/48, Airfix, 2018</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/airfix-albion-refueller/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/airfix-albion-refueller/</guid>
      <description>Very good modern kit from Battle of Britain: Ready For Battle set.
The Albion 3-Point Refueller Not much information available online about this machines. Refuellers like this were in use with the RAF during the Battle of Britain. Apparently having 3 fuel hoses cut down the refuelling time.
Model quality Almost no flash, great detailed instructions, excellent fit, good decals. Just perfect.
Build notes The build was straightforward, no fit issues at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bedford MWD, 1/48, Airfix, 2018</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.ru/models/airfix-bedford-mwd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>//models.bulimov.ru/models/airfix-bedford-mwd/</guid>
      <description>Nice little model from Battle of Britain: Ready For Battle set.
The whole kit is fantastic - it&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;new tool&amp;rsquo;, so perfect quality and level of details. I&amp;rsquo;ve decided to start with truck just to learn how to paint vehicles and try some new techniques. It&amp;rsquo;s the first model I&amp;rsquo;ve painted after I read awesome Adam&amp;rsquo;s Armour book by Adam Wilder, so I&amp;rsquo;ve tried to apply knowledge I&amp;rsquo;ve got from the book.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>