<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2023 on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</title>
    <link>//models.bulimov.me/tags/2023/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2023 on Alexander Bulimov&#39;s Models</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&lt;br/&gt;&lt;small&gt;&lt;small&gt;  &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Creative Commons License&#34; style=&#34;border-width:0&#34; src=&#34;//i.creativecommons.org/l/by-sa/4.0/80x15.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Content licensed under a &lt;a rel=&#34;license&#34; href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/&#34;&gt;Creative Commons Attribution-ShareAlike 4.0 International License&lt;/a&gt;, except where indicated otherwise.&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/small&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//models.bulimov.me/tags/2023/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[WIP] HMS Flirt, 1/64, Vanguard Models</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/vanguard-flirt/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/vanguard-flirt/</guid>
      <description>This model attracted me because of graceful, beautiful lines, and my desire to try a recent model by famous Chris Watton. After all, I quite enjoyed his design in Lady Nelson, and the kits from Vanguard Models had glowing reviews on a Model Ship World forum.&#xA;HM Brig Sloop Flirt There is nothing remarkable about ship herself. She was built in 1782 and had a relatively uneventful career in the Navy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2023 Year in Review</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/2023-year-in-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/2023-year-in-review/</guid>
      <description>Continuing the series of retrospectives, let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at year 2023.&#xA;While in a global, geopolitical sense the year was just as bad as 2022 (at least from my perspective), from the modelling standpoint it was actually fairly good.&#xA;On the surface of it, I only completed two models. But it&amp;rsquo;s the model that count, not the total number.&#xA;HMS Terror I&amp;rsquo;m delighted that the dreaded HMS Terror is finally finished!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HMS Terror, 1/75, OcCre</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/occre-terror/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/occre-terror/</guid>
      <description>Once I built up some confidence with wooden kits, especially after St. Gabriel I felt confident enough to start the &amp;lsquo;proper&amp;rsquo; wooden ship. Like you know, one which you have to plank manually and scratch-build most of the stuff. As you probably know, picking the right subject you are really interested in is the key to success. Especially when built is expected to take many months. After careful considerations and reading Model Ship World a lot, I picked this kit from OcCre.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>24ft Cutter, 1/64, Vanguard Models</title>
      <link>//models.bulimov.me/models/vanguard-24ft-cutter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//models.bulimov.me/models/vanguard-24ft-cutter/</guid>
      <description>This tiny kit was purchased to compliment HMS Terror.&#xA;OcCre provided cast metal boats with Terror kit, however I lack artistic talent to make them presentable enough to pass for wood.&#xA;For this reason I took measures of biggest boat that was intended to be put on ship&amp;rsquo;s deck, and ordered similarly sized boat kit from Vanguard Models.&#xA;Model quality It is made by Vanguard Models, by legendary Chris Watton, so I had no doubts the kit will be great.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
